# **Juliette Gondon**

New Haven, CT | Phone: 860-878-5491 | Email: juliettegondon@gmail.com LinkedIn GitHub

# **Summary**

Creative and energetic Full Stack Web Developer with experience in design, digital content creation, and tech marketing. Delivering smart design solutions to smart people.

Keen on designing aesthetically appealing web interfaces with attention to detail and brand awareness. Skillfully implemented innovative web development concepts in a team setting to more efficiently create full stack projects. Bilingual in English and Spanish. Recognized for being a strong leader and communicator and taking initiative.

## **Projects**

#### E-Volve

Repo / Deployed App

Tasks included designing and creating the MVC for React app, implementing routing with API's, and implementing CRUD database functionality.

### Franklin Products Employee Management

Repo | Deployed App

Responsibilities were creating different login routes for different types of employees, and designing the UI while matching the company's pre-existing brand design using handlebars.

#### **Dinner with Developers**

Repo | Deployed App

Core responsibilities included webflow, and using HTML, CSS and JQuery to construct and display the outcome of our API calls.

# **Languages and Technologies**

- React.is, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.is, MongoDB, MySQL, React-Router & Express
- o Progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory
- o Tools: VSCode, CLI, Heroku, Git, Final Cut Pro, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom, Keynote

## **Education**

*University of Connecticut School of Engineering - Full Stack Web Development Certificate* 2020-2021

**Quinnipiac University, Hamden, CT - Bachelors of Science in Health Science Studies** 2016-2020

# **Experience**

## Educator | Iululemon

New Haven, CT | 2019 – present

Educating guests on product, creating experiences and fostering community connections. Lead educator of diversity and inclusion. Working in a team dynamic - recognized by local and regional managers for being adaptable, flexible and eager to learn. Motivated and extroverted team player with proven success in customer service and cross-team collaboration.

### Content Creator and Social Media Management | Juliettiful, LLC

New Haven, CT | 2014 – present

Owner & writer of Juliettiful.com. Self-taught in SEO, email marketing, word processing, collaborative work, and budgeting. Privately managing web and social media for multiple clients. Maintaining a personal blog and digital brand including content creation, post planning, and adherence to brand identity to portray blog's image via digital media. Gained 10% revenue growth completely independently from 2019-2020.